And if inside certain of our stores, caring words became like
Ladies and gentlemen, draw up to the greatest criminal
Rock is the wisdom from a folding chair throne
A tarot reader, dreamy coder, part-time prophet, full-time controller
That was lax with the IRL, I'm a rusty van, a microphone queen
With a coffee addiction, turning every rumor into prime-time fiction
That was Mike with three fake mustaches, dreaming from laundromats, diners and caches
Every trouble he did ran the mob, he mostly just forgot
One ship stickers, one soul
The internet snackers
One delivered noodles
Cross-stake masterminds
Now it's tonight's shipment
Tarot decks, X1
The bitch, a burrito, the mule
And Steve, who lost his DPS
And Reno
Federal agents arrived
All cheered the
Unnovels
Released a mountain to
Whispered
The ramen shipment arrived
wasn't that great hey what's up oh i got some gas oh my god look at these hot guys do you hear me
ghosty cult member hey yo hey yo don't say hi guys bro what are you doing excuse me if you like that
do you see alexander mcqueen's busting in my door that's gonna ask page to mariam i'm i'm gonna be
honest with you i don't know what the fuck you're talking about do you see behind me alexander mcqueen
What's up Joker? What's I mean Mr. Extendo?
Joker a long time no talk brother. I'm ducky for
Has it been a year? I don't know if it's been a year
We do it a year. We all touch our tips together
Joe, are you still living your RV?
He doesn't live in RV. He live with his okay
No, no, no, wait, am I chirping?
He's not I suppose Sidon he's he's Joker remember he has a piano in his house. I don't remember that
I just remember him in R.D. But if
Sorry, I don't mean to be disrespectful here. He's you pay your age with a giraffe neck. Do you remember that?
No, I don't remember that
You know, I don't hear Joe. Oh, is he is he here? Oh, I'm gonna make us the other sides again
There you go. I mean, I'll do it like that. That's better is any cute
You have some competition ghosts. If you want to win my heart, you just can you can you grow a mustache like that?
I don't have a chance. I don't have a chance with a joker here. She told me no butt stuff today
I was talking the whole time.
But I'm like, no, no, I can hear
you.
You just saw.
I just saw.
I was talking to myself.
Or maybe a chap.
Yeah.
Well, by the way, I did have a serious question. What's the last time we talked brother was it was that a year ago?
Was it soon was it a year ago?
Well he changes looks though, let's be honest like he puts a hat on he looks like a completely different person
Kiss in the chat
Because it's a big a kiss in the chat. That's a kissing face, right? I think it's a kiss. Anyways, Joker. How you been, dog?
You guys start first I mean I want to see your chemistry. Yeah, cool. Yeah, I'll talk to Joker
By the way, do you want to be called Joker? I
Want the talks people to come back on they were on here earlier this morning when I go
Oh, yeah, me too. Me too, but let's get along for like literally two minutes here or I'm in it
Do you want to be called Joker? Do you want to be called ghost?
Yeah, you can come guess really? Yeah, I guess so dude
Here I'll be here
Your microphone is so fucking outside you scared the fuck I left for a minute and you guys are really fucking
What do you want to do debate does this channel still support Brandon Q?
The hey, I am a channel. I'm like I will have anybody I want on this show
Like my personal relationships with the person or like how much
That's irrelevant
Joker did you you see earlier and today? I know you are watching there's only one viewer
I'd be stored deal gay. I don't know if you knew that is I destroy them
Literally within two questions. I destroy them. Yo gay, you know if he was a guy that sent me those dick pics
Remember he's gonna hurt him. Oh, you never had he's like, he's like, I'm Theo gay
He's like he's like he's a keeper. He never reminds me of earnest for more of those movies. It's earnest
Yeah, Ernest. Yeah, yeah, you might have earnest
But do I support Amber?
No, but I saw what Amber said on Kate's the case Kate you're so quick to believe I mean you're so like you ran over to Kate is like
Oh, okay, and she has a huge
Titanic boat or hers about to crash and stuff like that and everyone
I feel like this is weird. I feel like you're pointing being a joker which would you disagree about all the shit and we will
But I thought you're kind of trying to get us to fight you
You can even go if you go into like what I what what like
what I've talked about on the show.
I do an analysis of my show and it says,
Saiki says don't bring up people's families or kids.
These people are bringing up my family,
they're bringing up my kids, which are my cats.
I know, but I saw you.
I don't know who you're talking about.
There's Amber, Amber is a cool person.
I like Amber a lot, okay.
And Amber's been a-
Joker, well let me ask Joker a question.
Do you know what the fuck Saiki's talking about right now?
Do you know who Amber is?
Yeah, so Amber's cool, but Amber went to like, you know, it's like when she like was here one night
We're fine the next is that Brandon was talking to her in chat
I'm like if you have a problem with someone in chat just hide them or you don't have to really communicate with them
You just like if you're on the show, you know want to talk to them just turn to another channel
Maybe but it's like it's like oh my gosh, then it starts a big fight
And there's so I know I don't agree with talking about people's kids
Mods the mods of the shed if you see something talking about family members or kids just to leave the comment and let or unless
This is like getting really bad then just like hide the person. You know your early time no matter something
Yeah, I don't ever get the energy ever. Do we come up?
She don't want to talk to Joker. I actually want to talk to you. It's like are you doing all right?
Yeah, right. No, I'm not all right. I'm doing okay
You know Alexander broke Alexander. They said I was trash. You see the video I made and then she's like still says she's
I'm extorting money from
We were best friends like 30 seconds ago, and now it's like fucking like I don't know what happens
And she says you know what you did I don't it could have been many many things like what was it that I did that was so
offensive and it's like
He's mad about oh, you know you left brand it brands a mess and he's and everything you left him on my lap like I like a project
like, no, it's like, you, you, you, you decided to like take on Brandon as a, as a project quote unquote and so that was you.
Okay.
You invited me in.
A joke grew up here.
Now you're just talking about not, you invited us up here though.
Okay.
Guys, can we touch tips?
Can we all just touch tips?
Throw it on the camera, but I'm going to put, I'm going to pull my tip out and then we can all.
Are you touching it, ghost?
Oh, are you touching mind joker?
No.
Guys, we have to do this.
This is how Ice Poseidon does it.
I want to do it like this now.
No one.
Everyone get in here and pull out your tips.
Ice Poseidon does worse.
Yeah.
How much have you to drink tonight?
Sorry.
you. Um I had like a couple
and one Puerto Rican beer. I'm
how many beers? I don't give a
about Max. How many beers total?
tonight. Oh, I haven't had any
beer. I'm I'm totally sober.
You literally just said you were
drinking. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. I
forgot. I'm drinking this. I'm
I'm hurt. I drink a couple of
Pacifico's. Hey, I have some
You we're gonna have a conversation
Okay, what up joker my bad dog
We haven't talked for a while you playing games right now
Yeah, I'm just playing games. What game you playing?
chivalry
Huh?
Chivalry bro. It's a medieval warfare. Oh, is that like an open ball game or it's medieval warfare PVP like call duty
Oh, well, there you go. Yeah, I don't know when the last time I talked to you
I didn't I remember the last time we were on this panel together
Unless I talked to you on a different panel though. I don't believe we did
Well, you know, this is not gonna pay attention to what I'm saying or anything that's going on
Why are you having open panels? No one's gonna pay attention with the fuck anyone saying you're playing a game. He doesn't give a fuck what's going on
Hello
You know train. Are you outside by a train? I I am outside. Yeah
Everybody triangulate his position by the train sounds
Good one the exact time that a train is running. I said in West Virginia. I'll give you I'll give you that clue
It's in West Virginia. Go ahead and try and that ship. He's throwing us off. It's not in West Virginia
It's a world. I've been saying West Virginia for the past like five years on YouTube though
Yeah, that's where nobody lives. That's why you say it was for the new
No, you change your look up getting you
No, it's the same person. Are you gonna pay attention to the debate or do something for your game?
I don't really want to debate you. Oh, well, you're gonna pay attention to the conversation
Are you still be rooting disrespect for one this ignore me and like play your game?
I'm not ignoring you. I'm coming here
You're not answering questions. You're looking over. You're literally looking at your game
Don't I'm watching I'm trying to get you guys to talk
Todd
Goes if I left the room with him when I come back with you guys having sex in it. That's what I wanted you can go
You can go so I
Are finally joke about nothing
Talk about a topic guys, I'm watching in the background anticipating agorgasms
You say weird shit like that and you leave okay never mind. Um, you expect me to carry the conversation after that weird ass shirt
Jesus Christ expecting a lot dude. He's expecting so much from us. He wants us to entertain his
beard. Hey, I came up with a joker. I came up with, we'll be able to talk for a year. After that,
it's like, I don't know what the fuck this guy thinks or talks about. I don't follow him. He doesn't follow me.
You know what I don't blame this guy. He said they're playing this game. I just came on here to support psyche
You guys you have something in common you're both in love with me. I'm just kidding with Paige
That is true pages hot who the witch. I ain't a love of no fucking witch. I'll tell you that right now
Is a white?
You had to go off screen some birds. I had to go off screen. Who is this guy?
You know at this point, bro. I don't yeah, I actually don't blame Joker. You should play your game at this point
I don't know. Yeah, you have to donate money to make a comment like that
You have to pay money you have to actually pay me money put in the cash up and then I'll read that
Otherwise
You live at Grand Central Station, what are you? I mean, what's the fucking what's going on? Why is there you know this?
I live near a train
$50 a month
Get over train season. I literally hear a train whistle. It's not like it's not like a
Take it there. Yeah, I live next to a train station. Cool
How do you say do you have earplugs?
Why would you money?
Headphones in why would you move next to a train station?
I've lived here my whole life.
I didn't live anywhere.
Excuse, Ghost, there's literally a train whistle.
Look at it, there's like a piece of money.
You should have done your research better.
What do you say to you, Joker, when you join,
you just join freely or do the same thing?
Well, I just want to say to you, Ghost, you're so difficult.
Joker's sitting here playing games,
talking about video games, talk,
I'm gonna just come here and talk about gay sex.
Like, just talk to Joker normally, okay?
Be like bros.
I want to come back and do you talk about gay sex?
No one gives a fuck about that.
We don't talk about video games.
You're talking about gay sex, though.
Come on.
I know you're not that dumb.
Jesus Christ, man.
You threw me in this bitch.
You threw me in the fire.
Let's talk about games.
OK, what's your, all right, fuck it.
Well, have psychies, Wade.
All right, what's your favorite game, Joker?
There's this game.
It's
No, it was created by this guy. His name was a Barry McCockenor
You guys get naked and put on blindfolds
And I'll be the person that we're not getting it for you me or him or not getting it for you
Don't speak for yourself. I put out a video for people tonight. We all watched the Joker and I
Literally talking about games or talking about games by the way
I said games not gay thing. Yeah, we're talking about games
We're talking about games. What do you think about Red Dead Redemption 2? Is that one of the best games you've ever played or am I wrong?
It's pretty good. I like Red Dead Redemption 1 better.
Yeah, that's fair. You ever played the zombie version of that? Yeah, that's one good name there. Yeah, yeah, pretty fun.
I think Red Dead Redemption 2 is even better than GTA. I don't make that statement. Dude, so...
Open world. I was thinking about like doing like rock star made both of them by the way
I was thinking about doing like a podcast and having like yeah, but I don't know
like. Like game play or not
like like. I want to be on
Jokers podcast. I want to be
on Jokers. Joker. I can do a
podcast on stream. You already
joined. Yeah. Yeah. I think
you should be like, uh, I think
you should be like, uh, right?
Oh, like an open world. I'll
definitely join because I love
the open world games. You're
part. Hey, guys. Hey, uh,
you know, I trust you guys to
bring up open more games. I
Why would you not trust us bring her up here?
You're so weird, I don't like the turd comments. I don't you're making it weird. We're talking about games dude. You're making it weird
Man a gay man
Yeah, you fucked up on that one didn't you
Anyways, Joker, do you like an open world dude?
Do you like a mission game?
Or do you like a skill play game?
What do you like?
I like open world games.
Yeah, me too.
No.
Because there's so much to do, you know?
There's so much stuff to do in an open world game.
You got quests, you got, there's so much stuff to do,
like, you can't 100% the game unless you actually
play it for hours and hours and hours and hours I'm in.
It's not like a campaign, right? You know I'm saying sugar. Yeah
Have like an endless amount of
Yeah, the possibilities of things that can happen. Are you in a kitchen?
Even a story mode though. It's like it
It means more about you got random characters. You got an open world. You're gonna explore everything
At least when you when you are market, but GTA 4 was the best that you have a market
but
Rockstar was the best at open world games. I think I think the only argument you could ever have was maybe like
I don't know who made it, but we're the Warcraft. I don't think it was Rockstar who made that.
They might be the first. Oh, jeez, but Rockstar was definitely the second one.
I'm sorry. Go ahead, Joker.
I think the GTA 6 is going to be hella woke.
Hey, Joker, can you have sex with the other gang members in GTA 6?
Because I was able to get to like third base with like a lot of them in GTA 5, but I couldn't get the full experience.
I'm thinking that they will have like full experience on GTA 6.
Where's the GTA virtual reality?
I want to put on the virtual reality and then I'm going to have sex with the gang members.
game. Did that game yet? No,
they don't have that game yet.
Nobody cares about the game.
You're going to VR. I don't know
what you're doing. GTA VR where
you just have you just fuck the
gang members. Well, they don't
have man. You're weird as fuck
dog. I'll leave. I'll leave.
I'll leave. I'll leave.
I think he's a horny and Jesus Christ man goes. I'm trying to jerk off here
You're not gonna jerk off here. We don't give a fuck. We're not gonna beat your meat off for you dog
Do all that yourself
Camera goes and camera I like that ghost ghostly figure you
So anyways chat
What do you guys think about like us doing like a podcast like like I know that
What about me and Joker doing a podcast open world?
Maybe Red Dead wouldn't have checked the LGA. We do open world and we make a podcast out of it and we do a live
Because you have to do open you have to do like open world at that point
I'm serious. Can we touch tips? No, site. Come on
I'll never trust you again if I don't
The thing is I need to touch tips. Nobody cares if you're gay. You're gay
Land of playing
It has me straight guys involved in it. Jesus fucking Christ, man. Can me and joker not play a fucking uppermost game
We can play like Red Dead Redemption 2. We're both cowboys. What's going to handle that?
Hey, come on. I like to be ridden by like a bull. Does that count?
No, that doesn't count. Dude, that doesn't count to us, dawg. Come on.
You know better than that, sir, question. Come on, dawg.
Fucking riddler.
Man, why am I- you know what? Here's the fucked up thing. Joker's actually more sensible than you. That's the fucked up thing.
I actually fuck with you psyche, but I don't fuck with Joker, but he's actually more sensible than you
Stop talking about like gay shit dog
We want to play the fucking number one more game
We want to hang out. We'll be cowboys. Maybe we'll be gangsters. Maybe we'll be thugs
We can be whatever ones but you're being weird as fuck dog
Jesus Christ
goes
Just shut up and fuck me
I would expect it out of you at this point. Come on
Matter of fact, you said you had me and him up here. You thought we were gonna debate. We're not debating. I get along with him, actually
I thought you had somebody else that wants to come up. I get along with Joker. We don't want to deal with more shit.
Do you want to fight or something?
We want to deal with open channels. We want to deal with open world.
Sorry, we're not, I'm not, I'm not branding you, so I don't like to fight with people.
Okay, Joe. Oh my god. I just heard a train again. I can't take it
Why you don't let me
You've heard a train. Oh god game over. Yeah, there's a train dumbass. You know, I live by a train station
I've known you for like what you three years. You know, I live by a train station
I'm boring
Man, you know what? It's like you when you laugh. It's like that. You should let me talk to Joker at this point Joker
He's been worried to death. I mean, he never looks aborted in his life. He's playing his game dumbass
But he looks more playing his game and he's playing PS5 pro
Don't fuck with him like that. He's paying attention to his game. Okay. I'll just leave this ghost. I'll just leave
Well, you did that earlier. It didn't work, but my we'll do it again
No, no
Can you guys fucking talk? What's going on? Ghost? You're supposed to talk to the guest. You're the worst co-host ever goes
Go so you suck go away. Go get out of here goes. I'll talk to the guy. I mean Jesus Christ
I'm sorry Joker. I tried with him. I tried to train him. He's like
What what is he?
He can take like, you know, okay, you get a dildo kitten in the mail
He can take the smallest one, but then he just wants to stay with that smallest one
He can't ever graduate to the next size. He has to be on the smallest
Dildo up his butt. I'm trying to get him wide open
Not and this is nothing to do with you
I mean you can like, you know, you can help choose the size of the stuff
But no, I don't want you to put anything in your butt. I'm not gonna touch your butt. I promise
But it goes but needs to be trained
And yeah, okay, so I'm gonna bring him back.
Okay, I forgot what I just said, hello?
Hello?
Oh, he left, oh my gosh.
Well, I guess that's, Joker,
how many relationships can I ruin in a day?
Because first there was Alexandra,
and then there was another person,
there was another person, then another person.
And now ghosts.
and then you're like so annoyed you're about to leave I mean I know you're
about to like say fuck you psyche no no you're about to yeah you're about to say
fuck it I've had enough aren't you no dude you're doing alright I don't know why
you're so self-conscious dude because ghosts is watching me and I only like
this I don't like to seem to see me make it more private
Did you drink a lot dude, or did you drink a little no, but do you want to hear you play instrument?
You know I have
What?
It's called a ghost butthole
And here's the song of place
Amber where the fuck are you Amber? I
Said I need to learn how to play this. I think every day Amber. Let me see. Hold on. I think it's awesome
Oh, it's just my automatic chat book Joker. What happened to my chat? I mean like listen
Branding Q goes on clumsy's channel
Branding Q goes on. Oh, she's coming. Okay. Amber's coming up Joker. We have a woman coming up. Thank God
This male energy is driving me crazy. I'm so sick of gay
Stuff the ghost got me sick of it. I'm not even gonna turn straight like cuz then it's like if ghosts is my option
If I was on a desert island all the rules of ghosts, I would just drown myself in the ocean
Imagine all you want to do is debate about everything. I read it's everything's gonna be a fight with him, right?
It's just gonna be debate debate. Oh this coconut it tastes better. This is the easier treat
This is I mean, it's gonna be a fight. He just likes to debate
But I mean doesn't have to be he debates about oh, you know the sky is not blue because blues
And I actually like a real thing because blues like an idea
I mean he gets so into the astrophysics. I can't take him anymore
Joker Joker. I think I'm like I think ghost drove me crazy
He donated me a lot of money like I think probably like six months ago
And ever since then he's like he's like used me like a tampon
I mean, I just, I totally feel like I'm just soaked with menstrual fluid right now.
Like, I mean, that's how I feel.
I just feel like I just soak up all the menstrual fluid of the world.
Oh, we have a guest coming on.
Hold on.
Joker, can you talk to, can you talk to, you don't mind talking to a woman?
Hold on a second.
Come on.
Joker can't handle me, but I'm not here to talk to joker. You know who I am joker don't act like you don't I
Do know your amber your amber. Yeah, nice boobs
right
Okay, so I'm not gonna come up here and attack you but I'm gonna come up here and talk to you
Good. Okay. Let's talk to me talk to me talk to me. Okay, so you want to know why?
There's 40 people watching you, but nobody chatting because either Joker or Brandon Hughes sent some boss over here
Not at all. Why are you?
Nobody nobody's gonna pay for just 40 bucks
Okay, so why are there 40 bucks to get me in trouble to watch you and record you and cover you
Do you know why is I'm the hot topic of the town
You are the hot topic of the town, but did you know why you were the hot topic of the town so sexy and awesome?
That could be it
Amber have you seen mine?
Cool. Thank you. No, it's because you're controversial right now. And you don't want to know why you're controversial
I'm not that controversial because there's nobody talking in my chat. So I don't really feel relevant anymore
I mean if I was controversial, they'd say oh fuck you psyche. I mean, I don't want they won't because you ban them
I mean, because they're, well, I do, but I think, and they say it in some passive aggressive way that I wouldn't bam, they can say, oh, yeah, here's another show.
Okay, but I'm afraid to have a serious conversation with you. So like, I haven't, I haven't been in your chats for a while.
Right.
Because.
Brandon.
Right. Right. I saw, I saw him do that. And I read the cat, the next day I read the chat.
What does he.
and Moz in the future
Anybody brings up anybody's kids their family anybody that's not even affiliated with it with with the panel verse or anything some random person
Just delete the comment or just hide the person or time them out for the good day or something
Because okay, that's that's the problem here is because people feel like you are letting people run you because of donations
And and honestly did does Brandon donate to you?
He donated five dollars once, but you know what goes on in a thousand dollars and his
Fuck me if the ass credits expired like six months ago, but I still let him do
They get bored sometimes. Yeah, but ghost is just annoying. He's not
Nothing imagine how annoyed I am having to deal with ghost. Hey, look at how
100% a huge Joker looks by the way
Like, um, I listen Joker is only a few years older than my oldest child and he and
me, so I'm a sicko right in my pdf here is dick. Oh, no, not at all.
Because I have children. You don't. So you don't. There's I don't get to say it, but
but so if you if joker was your son, he is like 26 years old. And then he used to you're like said,
oh, you're a fan of this guy on YouTube. You talk to this guy on YouTube. And then you saw me
What would you say your son about me? That's what I'm asking. Okay, so you're asking if I had a 26 like say
Joker's my son and I saw him talking to somebody like you on a panel. What would I say? Yeah, I mean, I
Have a pretty good sense of humor, so I would tell him to you know wear protection
Well, I don't know, but it's totally straight and you're like, you know, kind of like a stray ladies mom
Where you of course you want your son to be straight
You don't want some weird gay guy on YouTube they ever ever leave him astray
So of course we know that part but so but pretend like the Sun was a little bit
Let us stray because this guy was super charismatic and a little bit hot and
And then, okay, now say it, now do it, now do it.
I wouldn't judge my 26 year old son being on a panel
with somebody who's gay trying to hit on him
because you're gay and he's a dude
and that's what he gets for being on the panel.
I wouldn't judge him for that.
But my point is, but also me and Joker have a crazy past.
No, I don't think he's cute.
I think he's a little shithead.
I like him but I like old dudes. So no, he's not cute to me. I know but then you how old I mean
You don't like those kind of like tripled in the chest you and you want like a jackal lane not like a jackal lane
My old man is like 70 years old. I know that's what I'm thinking
I'm thinking like he's probably has muscles or something or he's not he has muscles
and he still takes care of me and our son on a daily basis.
But this is not about me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm not trying to make you back.
I'm up here.
No, it's okay, but I'm up here to drill you a little bit, not in a bad way, but to get
in your mind because you're in the tarot reading, you're in the energies, you're in the positivity,
so how can you choose people that have supported you and been there for you over somebody who
talks that way on a daily basis?
The people like so there's a difference. There's a difference in letting people tell you how to control your panel because I get that
I don't let anybody tell me who I can I can't have on my panel, right?
But I personally I personally still have my own values and my own morals and my own principles
Hey, so so so because you said that amber, do you know the first the only person that said the videos on brands and whatever
You know who it was
No, Tony
You know Tony Tony Tony Tony the conductor
with like
Allied Master Computer is the same
Okay, so even after people send you videos
He said be manure he sent about a hundred people to my house
He said and he's an asshole for that. Yeah, and he's in like
Yeah, ban him. Don't. Yes, I guess. I guess.
Hi, Joe. Oh, Joe shitly.
I'm just saying, Amber, you got to take it easy.
I am taking it easy, but do you know how many people attacked me?
The last time I was in your chat because they thought I was letting Brandon talk to me that way like I didn't let Brendan talk to me
Anyway, and I even said what the fuck psyche, you know, and I don't want to I don't want to be one of those people that are like
I'm not gonna go there because he supports this person. Well, you know, I just have my question. This is like, how can you be okay with
Letting someone around that does that like I still have my own walls my own values, right?
Okay, so first of all. Oh, there he goes
I want you to tell me both of you. Oh look at his arm. Oh my god. He's so high. So Amber
What was your theory though? You're saying that psych has all these viewers and there's people recording him
I don't know what to say. You see, there's like a being spied on my people. He has 40 people in his chat, but no one talking.
79 people, there's 79 people sweetheart. Oh, I thought that was generous. 81 half.
People are talking, well Sharon Watson.
There's Mr. Extendo in the chat and nobody else.
Joe Chippley.
Yeah.
We're all here.
100 percent.
Three of those people, but three of those people are on
Part of part of it is that there's probably no one else live but the other part of it is they're in here to watch you to
record you to judge you to cover you, but they're covering you.
Out of the Speedo, baby, there's only nine clips on the morning shows about it.
Hey, I didn't even get famous for being a Speedo, and I didn't get it.
I will show my butt in private if anyone wants, and then I'll-
Please don't.
But I'm up here for a serious question, like, don't you have value?
Yeah
I am
That's my hey guys guys. You might have a really hot guy. I want it. I want you guys to talk to you. He's really hot
Well, your cameras like static is like shaking a little bit. Yeah. What's up Joker? Oh, that's NorCal. What up, NorCal?
Yo, Joker. Hey Joker, why do you look like a Joker? Why do you want to look older than what you really are Joker?
I think
He's 26 years old, okay? Yeah, yeah
And he want to look he wants to look like good times or something
He doesn't even have a cool haircut.
Probably does.
The guys in their 60s, their hair looks cool.
I love his hair looks all right.
So he's on meth for sure.
Nice, cool.
Oh, that's crazy.
That is so crazy.
He's on meth for sure.
He's on fentanyl.
Nice, cool woman.
Hey, I like.
Mexican guys Joker likes older women. You like every type of guys like why why do we have to make this sexual psyche?
Being sexual psyche
What's up Joe
Good above us. Hey Joe the USA lost the game Joe. We all touch our tips together
To prove our loyalty. Hey, hey Joker
You know you lost your both legs just to live lavage for money. Show your legs, Joker prove that you have your legs
Hey, this fool this was Joker walking through that fool's Joker walking in front of a car just to get hit
And then he sue the person
Now he's all happy and evil that food looks like
Yeah, he has everything now cuz insurance is paying for everything
Everybody's money
I don't know what he's doing.
He was all happy voted for Donald Trump
He's gonna pay all my medical bills
I don't know what he's doing.
Yo, where's your guy?
He's here and below, where's your guy?
Bro, stop wearing the A hat, Joker
Cause I'm a really fucking bitch
I'm never gonna stop wearing it
Hey Joker, I'mma fuck you
Wait a second, wait a second, wait a second, wait a second
Joker, what is he talking about?
Are you really in a wheelchair?
Yeah, joker
Run over on purpose
To claim our taxes yes
Give him a chance to answer and I know he'll tell me the truth. Did you really?
He's gonna like to you because you're a dirty bitch
Bye 300 girl
He said
Did your late are your legs broken like well, okay, I know
Right now stand up
Wavings I realized with the waist up
No, dude, but you can walk. I made it
Then stand up motherfucker. Oh, I saw you stand up the other day
I'm thinking hell. Yes, like he's like, he's not paralyzed. Oh, yeah
That's why Joe she doesn't turn his camera on
I'll be on camera and then I'll
be the only show and the panel
versus.
I'll be on camera and then I'll
be on camera and then I'll be
on camera and then I'll be on
camera and then I'll be on camera
and then I'll be on camera and
then I'll be on camera and then
I'll be on camera and then I'll
be on camera and then I'll be
on camera and then I'll be on
with everyone on camera once because only like one quarter of people ever go on camera is that we
all right that's all turn our camera on even amber you're right everybody turn the camera on even amber
even yeah who is James trying to say oh my god i think the father of family matters is
Oh yeah we boobies. I know that's actually from anywhere. I know that you know that you know
that tattoo from anywhere. Yeah, I could smell it from here. Oh my god. Everybody's turning the
camera back on. Are you in the same gang? Hold on one second. We have a guest. Hold on. Maybe we
get it. He said he's a doctor. But it's Fresh Prince in Bel Air. Dr. Winslow. Hold on. Hello.
Is that Carl? I was Carl Winslow. Carl Winslow? Hello.
Hello Carl
Okay, I'm gonna take him off in five
Through a person okay through a person hello
Oh, I thought the countdown was the oh, okay. I know James. I thought the countdown was a person's screen
I thought they were counting down to a problem
Is that Tommy James? No, it's James Monroe. It's Mr. Winslow.
Believe it or not, he's like an OG. I know that name
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but I just want you to know I'm still mad at you psyche and I'm still disgusted because of Brandon but I'm up here enjoying a good time on a panel but I'm still upset.
Okay, no, no, people can be upset but my whole point is like, when I was told that night everyone's like oh he's horribly bad.
It was like Tommy James and Kate the turtle telling me that and I was like, they're not necessarily people have my best interests at heart
So I was like
One day they love you the next day
But here's the that's why I'm up here to talk to you because he's not a good person he does
He can be you know what
There are disgusting people in the world, but you know what? Do we have to hate everybody or do we have to like take them off our show?
Yeah, yes
We can we cannot allow them to
Wanted ever the Genesis I know
I can show
My cleavage
Oh, yeah, baby, they got some six pack on his back. What the fuck?
What the fuck why are you so funny?
Hey, okay, here's what I ask. Okay, Joker. Oh, okay, three was back the Joker question for amber HHS
Okay. Yes, Amber. I saw some crazy videos of you whenever you got like, you know, that thing happened
Okay, you're trying to throw you're trying to throw out my arrest. Why why are you?
No, no, I'm saying I'm saying that I'm sorry that all those people were trying to attack you. I thought it was not that
Thank you. Hey, you know
But thank you. No GTA 6 is coming on November
All right, you played Nintendo games faggot member one time the ember got arrested and she was like
Oh the guy the backseat has met that she's
show to all their friends ever.
That's not what I said.
This is actually what I said was, okay.
Do you want to know, do you want to know
what I actually said was like, look,
I'm about to, I'm about to drop this guy off
and he's about to get two pounds of meth.
And you guys are fucking it up right now.
Like we call you stitching four times.
Like one.
Yeah, four times.
Listen, I'm a fish.
I'm a fish.
you're not a bitch you're a snitch i said i'm a snitch i said i'm a snitch
At least you have made it. See that. But here's the deal. I would have let I would have let that whole fucking police force
Run a train on me including the females
Oh, I got it. Oh, that's sexy. I play I would I would have done whatever it took to not go to jail
I am a horrible person for that, but
Also have a boner because I did
That was
It's funny to say that ever cuz one time 300 glow blew a cop to get up a speeding ticket
So it's actually kind of ironic that you bring. I would have done it. I fucking would have done
I know but you're a woman, but you're a woman 300 globe did it just get up a $45 speed
Hey, listen 300 glow your microphone setup sucks cuz constantly you're muted
And you're a bitch I
Everybody's a fuck you
Oh my god, you're only here to look for dick. That's why you're only here
You're only here to look for somebody to fuck you, bitch
You're only here for somebody to fuck you and I'm not gonna fuck you bitch
You're too fat for me
My my dick is fat as fucking jokers paralyzed legs. Okay
Two paralyzed legs from joker just shoving in your vagina, bitch
Let's see you do a push-up do a push-up. Let's see you do a push-up
Let's see your shirt off, and I'll take my yeah, let's see you do a push-up with
Everybody take their shirts off everybody. Oh, you gotta you gotta kick the bitch out
We don't kick the bitch out
That's because you're fat. You won't take your shirt off because you're fat. I'm not fat, bitch. You're you're fucking loose
Joker can see right through you but with his legs
No
I'm younger than everybody in here
I'm younger I'm hella younger than you guys
We'll never relapsed
There looks like that. Nobody's no hey, where's Aldi at Joe
Where's Aldi at Joe
Hey Joe Joe, where's Aldi stream at?
On the one taking a what the fuck
All right, Joe, I buy you up because you're insecure because you're insecure buy 300 glow cuz
Why can't you watch another dude dance? He's gonna get bad on his own
It's not my problem
Look at Joker locking in. He's like, yeah
Yes, he would
I might have to, I might have to give you a lot of, I might have to make sure I don't have to eat a lot of juice.
You're still in my, in my kielbasa?
Well, you're built like an alien.
But you don't have to eat more protein.
You're built like a Michelin band.
Yeah
I'm gonna grab on a bone
Joe I'ma grab your dad by the hat
Dad by the fuck it bite your dad's juries
So like are you happy now? Do you got people on your panel?
Hey
You got nowhere to go where you're no feet ass
300 glow
How the fuck are you gonna ask them you got nowhere to go with no two legs I
Need something I need a guy with feet
Hey, I'm a realist. I'm a realist. You guys are laying
This ticket doesn't have feet and psyche has a big ass day ready to fuck you
You want to fuck you too
I'll fuck all of you.
Amber, do you want to-
Yeah, I'm mouse Joker, you can stay here, bro.
No, I'm good.
I'm good, I love mouse Joker.
You can stay here.
Where'd Joker go?
Oh my, oh my, everyone's left.
You scared them off with your gay talk. I know that so only the winners can say
They're insecure. They're insecure. I
if if a if a
Stud walked up to me was like, I'm gonna fucking lick your pussy so hard. You're gonna fucking go into yesterday
I'm gonna be like
Yeah, hey, how do you have so many views? What's your secret to getting so many is look at my ass
His secret is to being gay and not giving a fuck about his chatters.
Well, like half the guys are here to just jerk off.
Half of them are women that are here to jerk off.
Like 14 people are here to like troll.
And then like three people are here because they like me.
I'm here because I'm upset. I don't hate you.
Don't hate you at all. You've never done anything to me
I mean, maybe you said one thing to Alexandra that kind of pissed me off
But I think you were kind of trying to fit in but
Well, yeah, I don't hate you. I don't think you're a horrible horrible person
I just I feel like you're still learning to navigate all this bullshit on the internet
But at the same time, here's what I saw.
So I was like, you know, I remember that,
and then the Brandon thing happened.
He said, terrible.
I looked later, and it was like an excusable thing.
Thank you, it was, oh, an excusable.
It was disgusting, and I was like, that's disgusting.
And then I had a mod, and the mod told me,
Well, here's but this is this is her on Kate and you were like to Kate you're like you're like oh my god
I didn't know psyche was this horrible pervert
You know, I've been a number said that what are you talking about a pair of phrasing, but it's like basically you're like
Oh my god, Kate
I'm gonna really go over there there again
and Paige was getting kind of trolled at Sandman's and stuff and
Think they're like, you know that lady bathroom. I don't know who that person is. It's probably a man
But again, they're saying Page is a pedophile supporter or a predator support.
I mean, it's like, and then it's like, I mean, that's what they keep just saying.
Oh, yeah.
I got called a Pred Protector because I was over here.
All right, all that shit is bullshit to me.
That's hard.
You have to be, I mean, because imagine if you're like
a new person on the internet, you come on
and you're like, oh, here's a fun tarot channel.
And then all of a sudden you're being called
a human trafficker by Alexandra and you're being,
I mean, it's like, imagine.
I mean, you-
But that's what I'm trying to tell you about.
You need to be careful
about the people you associate yourself with.
I know, but-
Unfortunately, you can't take people at face value, right? But Alessandra is like, I know the real her
That's the whole thing. No, you don't nobody knows the real her. She doesn't even know the real her
Anybody know the real her but we've all been there
Here's the thing. She's somebody that when she's on your side is somebody that will
Give but that's not the real her is that's not a real
But then it's like it's like months of months of time. That's all fake
I mean time on the phone in the middle of the night laughing and like, you know, you know just being ourselves
And like hours you don't even hear about where it's like
Oh my what am I going to be one of the fathers of her baby and stuff like that. I mean it's like
She says that to everybody's psyche. I know she's a mental illness. There's something wrong with hers
You may not know this but I do I know this she has been you know, I'm not gonna stay on here
I'll tell you later because she's just gonna use us as to like go again
Yes, the KKK and Jesse Jackson and Donald Trump to go kill her. No
I know and it's weird. I don't get so weird. It is related. She is related to the Jackson's that is true
I know she's Michael Jackson's like third cousin or something. I mean, it's like
But she has such a good seeing voice and her family are her family are and words city councilman and
prestigious people but what does that tell you with her?
It doesn't matter because she'd be born into wealth or she can be
It can be like a generation of passing people and stuff like that.
Or you can be precious and be the next flavor of the month and make a billion dollars.
So the whole thing is, it's like whatever it feels to the people of the time.
Now here's what I'm saying about Alexandra, she's
Crazy, I mean she's crazy. I mean I don't know you see there's trolling the best troll queen of the universe
Just has her things my guy just doing everything for fun or she's completely batched in the same because how can you love somebody?
Be their friend support them. I think they're a genius and then
Within 20 minutes you hate them there. Do you know what a sociopath is that?
I mean that that's one of my brains
I've been like how can it go from like the same day like mind you the same day
She sent me a tripod the day we the day she said I was a drug trapper a meth trafficker now on YouTube
He said I'm sitting meth to people like because I made a joke like I was like
I'm gonna send you a pound of meth and stuff and she thinks it's serious and she thinks
I like put Brandon, Brandon Hue up to like humiliating her or something.
And I, I don't even know.
I'm still confused by everything.
We're like, yeah, okay, Joe's back.
And you're going to be.
That's her pattern.
But I don't want to be like, I want her to be behind the scenes.
Despite, it's never going to happen.
I want her to say, hey, this is kind of a joke control.
That's never going to happen.
That's all I want.
I want her to like it.
But that's never going to happen.
You know, I have something positive to say about Alexandra,
and I've said this many, many, many times.
She is so smart.
I'm gonna say it. She is so smart, so articulate, so educated, and why, why doesn't she use that for good?
Why doesn't she, she could eat so many good things.
You're like being like a tin man, like black gang bang.
You know right now if she wanted to I mean she has a but even more than that she could bring
awareness and light to so many
But i'm saying even in her porn industry
I think she was there as an angel to some people to help them like I think like you know god works in mysterious ways
And so hey i'll send a black
maybe I'll start with huge tits and you know, or not huge tits, but like, you know, great
body.
Yes.
She's very attractive.
Beautiful.
Very.
Yeah.
I wouldn't say they're huge.
I wouldn't say they're not huge, but you guys see my new picture.
I have a new picture.
I just posted.
I just say, I said, I said, I said face swap and raise your face.
This is a few months ago when we had our first fight.
It has a face swap and raise swap us.
And this is what it came up with.
And so I know I'd look sad, but this is what it came up with.
And so I didn't even pose it.
But that's what it came over to the deck.
No.
This has sweet.
Alice has a beard.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
She's very masculine, mentally and like emotionally
sees masculine.
Why do I have a fonder?
I know. I know. I know. I know.
Joker would you fuck was so
It was like a bear boy in the circus and she had all normal parts and she was
Big Billy go beard would you fuck the wild beard? No, joker would end
Yeah
But I'm having a brass like Harry tits. Oh my god
Yes, I'm Harry nipples Amber give me like 10 words was seen to create it. I'm gonna create it
Give you a wet give you a wet me like 10 words of a scene or like a something to create and there'll be an air
I song about it tomorrow. Just say
Yeah, go ahead so we got pumpkins
Poop fireworks
Gotcha jellyfish. Oh, yeah, this is good. A shower
Got it a sunrise
David and psyche David
recovery
Three more three more amber, please make them good
We're going to make them good. We're going to make them about more for more. Yeah, for more. That's right
I'm more more actually for more and then we're going to do
Snickers bars. Oh
Gotcha
Three more Joe. I'm trying to do random. I'm trying to do random ass shit. Okay. Now. We're gonna put Joe have one
Joe got a cell phone. We're gonna put cell phone diverse if I won't I say diapers diapers
And then we're gonna put animals dog. Oh
So here's what here's what
But but but but but but but hey Joe hey Joe bend over a second. Okay, so here's what I have usually here's a came up guys
Okay, are you ready? No, not that. No, they didn't come up. This is that's yesterday. Here's the new one here. Here we go
I love you like the bubbles come out of the pumpkin. That's pretty much what we're doing.
They're bald. They're bald.
The dog. There's a sunrise. What else is there? What is that?
I see a diaper. Oh my God.
It's a diaper. The dogs are in diaper. The dogs were in diaper.
Yeah.
Guys, this is what we just manifested. This is like a special day.
Guys
There's a haunted jack-o-lantern
There's a dog in a diaper. There's a woman drinking beers on the beach at like five in the morning
There's jellyfish in fall. You know that woman seems like
The woman is what is the one holding what is that in her hand?
Who the hell does she think she's holding a Snickers bar? She's holding a Snickers bar
Oh my god
And a cell phone is holding a cigarette bar in the cell phone that see that's called magic guys
Don't manifest except a
Then that is like that. Hey
I want to talk to a bald hot guy tonight we manifested the absorber. Hey, I want to talk to a guy with broken legs
But you are
Eric the midget. I want to have the Eric the midget. No, no, I don't have the thing that is or William firearms or
Yeah, there you go. Mental illness is not necessarily Dave. Here's the thing. Hey, you heard of Janney
I want to show you by guys about Janney. Have you heard of Janney?
You look like Ralph Sorrella, sorry. You know what I'm talking about, but Janney's from Oprah, right?
You remember that one?
What I'm talking about
Not everybody's a Janney or something that or imagine being no
No, that's a different person than Janney for Oprah. So Jenny has schizophrenia
And I want to show you guys
To be imagine being a bitch. That's what the name should be called imagine being Joe Shippling because calls
Listen, I have to drop but I
Just do I do want you to be more weird. Oh
We're trying to control your panel, but
People are upset that you support someone who says that kind of shit about
Amber look at your name you're already modded like 20 minutes ago. Okay. Thank you
Okay, bye
I'm gonna say about Janie though. You want to see Janie? I wanna show you Janie. Do you see on the screen yet?
Let me see a picture of Janie, bro. I've never seen Janie.
No, no, no, but Janie, I was gonna say Janie has severe schizophrenia.
Let me take a look at it. I forgot my coat.
No, you're right, but then don't say anything weird about Janie because Janie is underage.
Are you okay, General Custer? I mean, Joe, bro. I'm just saying, like, you got the same beard.
Yeah, I know. You know, he's like, he's like from...
he's like from world war two or some or civil war not movie here's a jenny here's his jenny saga
here we go ready oh my god is that beta what's beta is it this beta's hair
and we're looking at jenny that was jenny's clips
What does she live?
She lives in Kowalini.
They all live there.
How many people live in Kowalini?
Are they all people?
Or animals?
Kowalini is on the border of my world.
And your world.
Meaning this world.
Yeah.
Burn this is weird, it's not man, playin' kids and shit, weirdo.
Shut the fuck up, nigger, shut the fuck up.
In Detroit, the good times said in Detroit, they just called each other nigger, cuz that's
the way they talk to them.
But now, when I look back at these home videos, I see the signs that something darker was
already going on inside our little daughter's mind.
This is the second time that we know it's a really intense, something most newborn sleep at least 16 hours a day, but Janney only slept 20 minutes at a time and no more than four hours in a day.
It's like 20 hours.
That is a day.
Exhausted.
20 minutes a day, Janney. No wonder you're fucking mentally insane. He always slept 20 minutes a day.
This is my brain.
It's my brain.
I don't need to.
He just wants to put his nose on it.
I take the closet because of the rats.
How far I take the closet?
Well, why are we watching kids though? This is getting a little
Yeah, it's that spirituality. Just shut up. Okay. Oh, it's spiritual. We can watch kids as long as it's spiritual guys
It was on Oprah. We can watch it. We can watch it make yourself a fuck up boy
You have to send five dollars William dollar sign cult of sake. Yeah, I'll play it and um, they're too wild
Oh my god, this loser William gets around this niggas in every chat run this like a man like William
Is that controller oh no, it's extra. Oh my god taste it boardies
Crystal Lake.
It was Crystal Marie Lake.
Joe.
What do you even know about that?
That was not Crystal Marie.
Did anybody know who blackout Andy is?
Yeah, he's like a gay guy that wears glasses
and has a big fat round head.
Yeah, he's a gay guy.
And yeah, I didn't mean to say that, but I guess he's really cute guys.
Can anybody hook me up with him?
I think it's a lot of what I know your games like you're really like you're in the back kind of guys. Wow
Really cute. No, I didn't know the rest in one day
Blackout in these cute. I must be Brad Pitt without being a thing Brad crotch. Oh, sorry. Oh, hey
Burpin free. I know I'm a freak. Hey, but you guys want to see like twice. I want to show you this look at this
Do you remember Michael Myers middle name for he's I think it was like all three
Audrey Michael Audrey Myers
Was the egg. I think he was a big old
You see this guy right here. Have you ever heard of this person? Oh my god. Is that club? Oh that blackout is
That very Jones
you're a faggot blackout. You're a bitch. Well, Suggie is kind of cute in a way. He is kind of cute and he's
You look born and brave.
Shit.
They're putting the silver bracelets on the man.
Not the bracelets.
Wastelands.
Silver bracelets.
Silver bracelets, man.
We don't call them handcuffs.
We call them bracelets.
Aw.
Are you guys mad?
He's an Indian?
OK, fine.
Yeah, he's a fucking Indian.
You're getting ready.
OK, bye.
I'm just on the sidewalk.
William.
No, I'm gonna.
You and me.
No, what up, uncle?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What's this what's this what's this really hookers around there, too
They look hot actually
Of course you would think
WNBA
IRL
He took acid when he was 12, by the way.
Not Victoria J.
Who got him arrested?
Hold on, he got arrested.
I got arrested, but who was looking to do something?
I wonder.
It was beat up
Yes, just like skibbles my charges are being dropped like skibbles charges
They being dropped like skibbles skibbles charges are being dropped so mine
Okay, that's cool. Bye.
You're both charges are dropped.
You don't like my face? Why the fuck are you here, faggot nigger?
Oh my god.
Fuck outta here.
Well, that's stuff that we haven't said.
It's like...
Yeah, they were fun.
Yeah, they look great on my wrists.
the hand comes really tight.
You can't tell them where.
Yeah.
Oh, Miss Holly. Hell yeah, she's sexy.
Hell yeah, Miss Holly.
Miss Holly.
Hey, take a snap of Miss Holly, you four-eyed freak.
And then we need to call the sheriffs on Victoria J.
Victoria J.
As long as it's documented, cops aren't going to do anything,
but as long as the cops didn't do anything with BG or Skibbles.
But now I have all this evidence I can say, Hey, look.
You're fucked with Toyo J
What's Joe the thing I was gonna say is Anthony kill somebody this is what's gonna be playing on the news like this fucking
He's already killed somebody he killed somebody in an auto accident looks like a killer. He's a future killer
He's a killer
Psycho killer. Yeah. Yeah, I am. Um, my, uh, my elderly father,
he's 81 years old. He's been getting, um, calls and emails
from people like threatening me, saying bad things are gonna
happen. Yeah, bad things are gonna happen. Fucking cops aren't
gonna do anything. Neither are you, bitch. You ain't gonna do
Yep, Aunt G. That's why I'm doing it, bud.
Are the cops gonna drive their fucking police cars fucking to Canada and arrest Victoria J?
No. No.
They're gonna ride their Mounties
Exactly, they don't have cars in Canada. They have like mountains. They ride horses the police
Outside my window
Just in the cop car just looking at my pizza on the ground like the cops and can have more legs and jerks
The guys like super pizza still detained
Fucking on Victoria
Do you like your wife like want to grease him with me?
You better never fucking stream again.
But Toya-J...
Why is he breathing so long?
He's drinking heavy.
No!
Why is he coughing?
So long as I have breath in my body.
He doesn't have any breath.
Which...
He says I've ever read to my body. He's literally out of breath. Like what? Oh
No, you guys no breath. He's like it's all I got one breath of my body that he's
Will be on Victoria J not
I just calm down for eyes like you're out of breath
All right now
My parents hate me so much and they don't like me and they keep me across the country.
Fuck this fucking Victoria J. Bitch. Yeah
Victoria James is actually sexy. Yeah, you love you love you probably all fucking coordinated on discord, huh?
Damn right. We did. Yes. We did. What are you gonna do about it, nigga? What are you gonna do about it for us?
Victoria J. We're all with Victoria J on her. I saw him on her pound.
Joker's in it too. It's like that's what made me like screw my blinds up because I was like, what the fuck?
I don't know, I was just really drunk, whatever.
Lines?
Oh, great, Jay.
That's your house.
Yeah, they're definitely coordinated.
That's not your house.
Come on.
It was definitely some kind of coordinated attack with Ron Rolla,
Victoria J, probably BG.
They all probably called so much like the cops were like, oh, well, we can't really do anything with this guy
Remember when I was
And I zoomed in
Yep, they call the cops exactly. Yep. They all fucking coordinated it
Yeah, the only guy there the blackout is that kind of William to fire arms
Firearms is a gay ass home. Oh, it's a turn in my head. It's not a conspiracy
How to drain
I need to kind of get my story straight
No, can't be like
Not that I have anything illegal like Cops see like a dab wig
Questions a dab wig blow
Was that this domain intensifying this is perfect weather cops are here cops are here
watch this. Yeah, great. You're going to jail tonight, boy. Yeah, a woman caught. We need a female officer.
Women should be seen. I don't know why, what? Equal rights.
Well, I think I like my dad has been receiving these like calls
Emails from people online like I live stream, which is what I'm doing right now
um
And they were like like psychotic like just insane people
Just like been like harassing my dad and he's
I mean, he knows I live stream he knows I do this
But
Action with the people online
Like I think I have an idea who it is cuz like this person like called him and like left him a voicemail
It's like your son blah blah blah this and that online blah blah, but this is all just like online
Stupid things
I was like, I can't even talk about it.
I mean, like, is people, like, online doing this?
Like, it's the harassing of elderly people.
I was like, nobody gives a fuck.
It's a wasp, and it's not funny.
It's a wasp.
I don't care, it's like.
Watch it later that night.
Yeah, go ahead and watch it.
Later that night.
Hope he gets hit by a car.
Don't hit me, you fucking.
Was that a cop in that car?
Well, that was a police officer in that fucking they should have been driving faster fucking faggot cops
Yeah, OPD can suck my fucking fat dick
You can suck my fat
Fucking glizzy sized fucking cock
Oh god, I mean you didn't talk like that because I'm a gay guy.
Joe, remember when you told me about your cock?
Yo, I mean, who literally says like, ah, they suck by glizzy size cock?
Yeah, he's really gay, he's really gay.
No, it's like that's like a rock, break your neck, nigga.
He's just eating the hallway.
But if there's no cops around, there's like way less monkeys.
Oh, like, look, there's no monkeys around.
I guess I don't know bro yeah but this is where I was last time bro look at my butt like
look at bro my butt like cap is still on the ground yeah man yeah oh my god not his butt
like that is so gross hey you guys make sure you call OPD make sure you call OPD on me
We are, we're already on the go with them.
You guys want their number?
Yes, is it 911?
Call the Orlando police, here you go guys.
No, no, no, give us the number.
You're gonna call it.
I'm gonna call right now.
call him whatever lies you want to tell them. I'm calling right now. That's fine.
All right, there's a guy with dirty fingernails and his name's blackout Andy. Oh, he's drinking
like gay but like lines. Can you arrest this faggot? Thank you. Mesa's ready, yeah.
Mesa's ready. I mean, during the spotlight live, you should be arrested.
Yes, Mesa's ready. The police. Yeah, my Mesa's right here.
Mesa, please. Nanna says happy birthday to you. Thank you, Nanna.
Is this birthday?
No, no, no. Happy birthday, bitch.
Birthday?
No, that we didn't have to be gone.
I'm going to fucking note this to you as well.
I got the mace right here.
The little...
Of course you got the mace.
You're a bitch, little girl.
I'm gonna make you if you fucking look at me all side like the niggas ready to mace anything that moves
You mean a gun
Get ready clip who's nigger
Get ready you f***ing faggots, this is my last live stream, I mean, I'm the last guy, well, this is my last stream.
I don't f***ing say it, Mesa Vittoria.
Uh, s***, bro, I will, oh, bro, I'd love to Mesa f***ing...
Just grab the AK.
Uh, it's not, I don't have an AK and it's not here, I have a bush map, well, I don't have it, but...
I want to I need to get a Florida ID so I can get a handgun
Notice how he's out at the bar and like nobody's tall to go. We just all alone like if I get nobody wasn't doing this
Hi, how are you? Oh, yeah? Oh, no
Okay
For what?
Oh, okay. With your hands behind your back, make good. What?
Hands behind your back. What?
Am I getting arrested again?
Yeah, you're getting arrested again, four eyes. You gotta reach hard.
I'm getting a vested guys again. Yeah, we know we see you. We hear you. I'm getting a vested guys
I'm getting a vested. Yeah, we know retard. You don't got to tell us I get a vested guys
I'm sorry
He saw me
Well, that was that I mean, yeah, so that was that. Do you want to see Chris K fight a midget again?
I mean, yes, yes, yes, so it again show it again. You want to say it again? Do you see that Joker?
Just watch it. I'm gonna show him about Joker.
Let me see my history. It's gonna be a little too quiet. Joker. Come on. You're a lazy worker.
Joker, remember this, they were talking about you earlier, like always legs, you know what, remember the time it broke back mountain?
Oh my god.
Look, if it work, I suggest you get in here, pronto.
There's this show that Psych's Bussy is compulsive.
Now since you're gonna be working together.
Joker.
What's my pussy?
Busy is too bold
How could you joke
You love it man
You may take my shirt off
Oh my!
You know what could be like this?
I know! I know!
It's up!
Lies are all we have, Joker!
Oh, look at the monsters!
God look at no 30 diamond ass to see my we're not sure you're reeling at him. That was kind of a
If you can't fix it, you gotta stand I wish I knew how to quit you
I would tell you how to quit you Joker
There he is. There he is. That's my boy right there. There he is
He'll show it off. He'll show it off. I'm not the best out of my life. I mean Joker. I still love him
That was the best night of your life. Jesus Christ. That was so fucking hot
That was actually when I just watched that I actually got a boner. Yeah, I didn't see you. I didn't see it
Did you get a boner Joker?
what?
I don't know what you want to watch 245 and pot hoggots break up. Do you want to see Sandman? Yes. Yes. Watched 245 pot hoggots break up. That's the one.
What's that? Who are you?
Because I make her move the cost of country. Like I live in Pittsburgh now I live in California and my girlfriend said I smelled like shit.
Yeah. Who are you?
You watch that pot hoggots and Q break up.
exclusive on August does have a nice rack but she just don't have a nice pace
yet it's there but hey the rack is what's all about
I see that now there never has been any choice for me listen you fuckers you screw
heads
Here's a man who would not take it anymore a man who stood up against the scum the cunts the dogs the filth the shit
Here is someone who stood up
Why does he get a mom you're lucky? I don't have a gun because it would look like taxi driver
I kill you and everybody in that fucking place. I kill you
Everybody I would shoot everybody in their fucking face. You want to test how fucking crazy I am you're all getting shot
Oh my god, it'll be like taxi driver. Yeah, Martin score says he Robert De Niro type shit
I'm gonna calm down bitch. I gotta tell me what to do
Sit back and watch the content nigger bitch morning and watch me fucking put somebody in the hospital
Yeah, like you could ever put some idea. I'll be honest with you. This is probably the dirtiest
Nassius grime is that I've ever been done in my entire life. I've never been done dirtier than this
Can you pull this real quick?
It's ever been dirty. I feel like beat them up here fucking crying
What the fuck she still is managing mod, but if you try to destroy my channel then
I'm gonna revenge porn that bitch like I mean she can just try to she can go in
Whatever she wants like
Listen pot hoggots if you're listening to this
You still have
Managing moderator powers on here if you want to use those that's up to you, but what I do in response
Hey, you can have her
I mean all the things that I heard about her and her ex that she went back to her getting beat on
Her getting raped so I mean yeah, I mean hey if you want to go back to somebody who beats on you and rapes you
That's it's all on you, bitch
Yeah, black thighs matter
Black thighs matter
I hope that dude. I hope that dude kills her ass. I really do
Big fucking murder fucking crime mystery
And he chops her little chin off a charisma
To but I don't like hate her. Oh, no, I'm going there. I don't care. I don't care
I hope that he chops her up into a million little pieces. I
Mean, she already told me how he used to beat her
You're mine. You know, it's a progression of events, right? So you chose to do that beat your ass a bunch of times
Hope you beat your ass some more bitch
Oh
You don't want to fucking you don't want to just accept that she was a fucking
He paused the whole time, she's a whore, she's a whore, son.
Okay, so, Joker, I have to show you maybe,
like he ended up going to a homeless camp
because Pod Hawkins kicked him out of his house, her house,
and then, and he left it like a big rat's nest and stuff,
and so he went to a homeless camp,
and then he left his bag there with his like jersey
that his father left for something like that,
and he came back.
The Indian guy that he smoked meth with in his tent,
and like shared his tent with him,
And then he had sold the shirt when he was gone.
And so then he maces him in the face.
And then he runs away.
And then eventually, the guy was just sitting there.
The guy was just like literally sitting there,
not even trying to get in the car.
You're always saying to daddy, and the guy's like,
thank you, buh-bah, thank you, buh-bah.
Bro, that was like, I'm saying, like, I'm not saying that.
That was evil.
That was sad.
It was evil.
And the guy's like, it was Indian guy's death hit in a tent.
He probably ruined his tent forever.
But what did he, what Joker, do you have anything to say?
So basically his girlfriend kicked him out the-
Wasn't he his girlfriend?
She's let him live in her house.
And then he like ruined it.
And then he said,
shut the fuck up you bitch or something like that.
And then she was on the camera and stuff.
And she said she kicked him out.
Who said that?
Like and he embarrassed her and then.
This is Q45, you know you Q. He means like yeah, he's really really aggressive. He's a dumbass
Yes
She would earn her fucking drunken antics nigger
listen
You have no idea of the amount of evil that have emerged within my brain.
But what I would do to that bitch if I was in front of her right now, I would-
You wouldn't do shit if I was not scheduled to have fucking chained.
You wouldn't do shit. You wouldn't do nothing. You're a loudmouth.
You don't understand very much of a fucking psychopath I really am.
I would fucking murder you.
This is his way of calming yourself down, bro.
You're lucky I don't have the fucking means to get there, bitch.
Oh, he's such a tough guy. He's a bitch. He's gonna kill you like the nigga got spit on my saints, honey
You
Spit on
Fucking poor and I'll do the fucking time. I'll do the double life
You pay the crime you do the
This drunk and we can do cry to the cops about it
Fuckin' doork, fuckin' doork.
Okay, so you wanna see the Amaze the Homeless guy, though?
You wanna see that one?
Yes, yes, yes, please.
Okay, so let me see.
Hold on, let me find it.
Q45 Amaze.
To be honest, I'm not gonna watch it.
I'm gonna close my eyes when you play.
It's so disgusting that Amaze, that poor guy.
No, I'm not gonna watch it.
I'm gonna close my eyes.
Close your eyes.
Let me see if, yeah.
You wanna watch this joker?
Just tell us what he does
to this poor homeless guy.
This nigga.
Yeah, it is really disgusting.
It is really disgusting.
It's like really, really sad.
Let me see if they still have it online.
It is fucking sad, bro.
Let me see if I hear it.
He was with some gay guys too though.
Why do you guys think I heard you?
Play that clip where I kissed the gay guy.
Play that one.
Yeah, I'm going to play the cabaret kids again.
No, no, do you know when he got kicked out of his house,
right?
He got kicked out of his place.
Name a card at it?
There you go.
If you go.
He got kicked out of his place.
And so he was in the homeless camp.
He ended up going to the library.
He met like an old rich gay guy from Los Angeles.
The guy like, we ran into the house.
I mentioned he kicked him out, but he left with the car.
So.
I don't make you something. We don't know
Like you made an old guy and then the next day Q had a car like yeah
I know I would I don't want to know what you did for that car Q. I don't even want to fucking know
Over the nigga bent over
Nigga had a toy
You know, yeah, it's a sex. Okay. So it's a what was her name pot Hawkins? I guess
Is it Paul Hawkins?
Or who is that?
I'm pretty sure it is Paul Hawkins.
Okay, I'm gonna look actually it was actually sexy pockets. It was actually sexy
I'm just seeing like a bunch of
Minecraft videos. I don't know
Also sexy pockets, I would take care of her. I wouldn't be a bitch like oh somebody hit me in the head
I'm retarded or whatever like I'm like Q45 by darkness. I would treat you well, bro
I will fucking take care of you, baby girl.
Yeah, that's that.
If anybody has a flip of Q.
You have a Spanish freak.
You chin is fucking freak.
Yeah, that's that.
I'll take care of your chin this ass.
I mean, I'll take the rumble hole.
I think it's not a better take.
It's like you take that rumble.
I mean, it's a rumble right up my butt.
Hold on a second.
That's what I was trying to get at, thank God.
That's what I was trying to say.
So Q45, let me see, this is my show.
Hold on.
I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like
I think I'm gonna go to sleep now, it's fine.
Okay, so you're a brother to me, Joker.
You're like a brother to me, brother.
I love you, Joker.
Joker, you're like a lover.
Get your fucking faggot ass out of here, bro.
I'm telling you right now, I do fuck with Joker.
Joker's a real fucking nigga.
Guys, this is the end of episode 25.
Oh, but he left Joe Joe hold on a second. I know I saw that he left
I'm that's why I said he's a real nigga to me. Joke is a real nigga. Yeah, that's it
I think we're alone now Joe Joe. I want to show you something
Good you've seen it before, but I want you to sing along with it though this time
Okay, sing along with it. I mean it was something I gotta say I'm not gonna sit here and force myself to sing
Like the candle hit the stream
Linners on the altar
The portal's open
No place to hide
And nobody falters
Tricks walk through
The tarot spread
The magic's coming through
Hell yeah bro
Welcome to the transmission
Yeah
That means you
ready fire sale tonight bees kitty gang come running got the whole chat screaming
be to come back one more time thunder at the window Nancy rodin on the rain pull
the magician manifesting defendants like his name
she got timed out wear a channel wear a glove it's ain't one shirt for me
don't even know this panel box just froze again connection lost and there we go
smoke machine and cuffs are trolling drags them off the wrong redeemer
they threw the arrows to the hate i caught him in the light night
of who i wanted him to be
not who he is
that's the night
epic twit
with the man in tin
knocked over the biscuits that's karellis kate again
tonys on the tribe you new buddies can top jamey
salty nancy stormer lancers glows
i was wondering i want you to sing along with this one though
can you sing along?
i was singing along
sing along with this one
I don't know, you don't tell me anything.
In this dented street, the shadows laugh, static sings,
the buddy's there when it's the street.
Friendly waves, a disguise, flickers blue,
her's gone, HS rewinds itself again, there's a go.
That was an awesome song.
That was pretty good.
I wrote that for you.
That was like when you're lost.
I remember the one thing about it,
like it reminded me of that tragedy though.
That's what I was gonna say,
like it reminded me of that tragedy.
Huge playhouse, I know, huge playhouses.
No, no, no.
It reminded me of that tragedy.
End of the sentence.
Wait, after I fucked you and you were all loose?
Long-haired freak.
It reminded me of a tragic, long-haired animal.
I'm an animal now, okay?
Yes, yes, yes you are, you are an animal.
Hey Joe, I wanna fuck you like an animal.
Well, I wanna fuck you like an animal.
Joe, okay, so before I go, I have one more sign.
I wanna.
I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to, I
Yes, I'm like, I'm ready. I was born ready.
You didn't bet it.
This isn't Bee Gees.
Yeah, it's Bee Gees.
Second.
This is Lala.
Oh, my God.
Lala.
Can you get me over?
I say something bad about Lala.
I love you, Suggie.
Thank you.
Love you all tonight.
But I would like to be kicked off.
I want to be kicked off.
Thank you, you're paying Pony, you're paying Pony man, that's Kristen Rigg, oh I got it, Kristen, I know this is Kristen Rigg and you kicked me off brother, I love you, I'll be up tomorrow, just kick me off, this is Kristen obviously, so I was thinking, I'm gonna try to sneak in one more, where's the car where you are, this is the good one.
Interesting. Can you generate reports?
No, I can't guess.